Guide to the Hartt School faculty collection ARCH063
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1930-2004
  - Alexander, Carlos, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Anderson, Everett, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Babineau, Ninette, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Badge, Ahlene (Mrs. Peck), Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Balsam, Arthur, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Beeler, Walter, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Benstock, Seymour, Circa 1946; Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Berman, Melvin, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Bilem, William, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Bilotti, Anton, Circa 1933, undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Blewett, Marie, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Bodenhum, Aaron, 1941 Apr 17 (Box Photographs 1)
  - Bonacini, Renato, 1967 Feb; Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Brawley, Robert S., Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Broadhead, Edward, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Broadhead, Helen, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Bronne, Ariana, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Bronstein, Raphael, Circa 1981; Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Bunnell, Lyman B., Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Burige, Susan, 1964 Oct 29 (Box Photographs 1)
  - Cavin, Suzanne, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Cheney, Timothy, 1964 Apr 21 (Box Photographs 1)
  - Clark, Walter Houston, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Cote, Collette P., Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Dadmun, Royal, Circa 1931; Undated (Box Photographs 1, Box Shared Small Oversized 2)
  - Depillo, Cesidia, 1942 Apr, undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Diemente, Edward, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Dinerstein, Norman, Undated (Box Photographs 1, Box Shared Small Oversized 2)
  - Doney, John, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Douglass, Geraldine, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Downs, Thomas, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Einstein, Alfred, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Ferrante, John, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Fidlar, Dorothy, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Fidlar, Wilfred, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Fonte, Henry, 2004 Mar 31 (Box Photographs 1)
  - Forbes-Davis, Joan, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - France, Herbert, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Freed, Isadore, Undated (Box Shared Small Oversized 2)
  - Freeman, Stanley, Circa 1948; Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Gaudet, Laura, Circa 1999 (Box Photographs 1)
  - Gelbloom, Gerald, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Giannin, Vittorio, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Gordon, Ray and Helen, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Groff, Frank, 1947 Dec 01; Circa 1957 (Box Photographs 1)
  - Hanson, Raymond, 1949 Nov 15; Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Hartt-Paranov, Pauline, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Hayes, Barbara, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Haynes, Lowell B., Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Herrmann, Virginia, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Hintz, Elmer, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Hubbard, Helen, 1962 Apr 03; 1966 Jan; Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Hubert, Marcel, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Iadone, Joseph, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Jackson, Douglas, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Jacobi, Frank, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Jacobson, Cecile, Circa 1954-Circa 1957; Undated (Box Photographs 1, Box Shared Small Oversized 2)
  - Jarratt, Howard, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Johannesen, Grant, Circa 1984; Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Karr, Gary, Undated (Box Photographs 1, Box Shared Small Oversized 2)
  - Kaschmann, Trude, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Katahn, Enid, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Katik, Ronald, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Kelsey, John, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Kleman, Rose, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Kopman, Israel, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Kroll, William, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Kugelman, Alex, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Kutik, Ronald, Undated (Box Shared Small Oversized 2)
  - Laderoute, Joseph, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - LaGace, Kenneth, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lagrutta, Aldo, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lane, Mary, 1955 Jan (Box Photographs 2)
  - Langston, Amy, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Larsen, Henry, Circa 1954; Circa 1973; Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lenom, Clement, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lepak, Alexander, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lewis, Brenda, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lieberman, Milton, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lischner, Rose, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Long, Grayce, Circa 1990; Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lucarelli, Bert, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Lurie, Bernard, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mack, Gerald, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Magg, Fritz, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Maison, Rene, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Malbin, Elaine, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Marijosius, Vytatas, 1954-1996 (Box Photographs 2)
  - Martin, Gene, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mase, Raymond, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mattran, Donald, 1968-1978; Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Maxym, Stephen, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mattingly, James, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mayes, Samuel, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - McKonly, Curtis, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Meier, Laura, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mende, Rose, 1957 Sep 10; Circa 1959; Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Metcalf, William, 1972-1977; Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mirovitch, Alfred, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mishkind, Abraham, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mitchell, James, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mizelle, Diana, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Moore, Kermit, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Morrison, Watson, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Mowe, Homer, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Muller, Dana, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Murtha, Roger, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Nackowsky, Jane, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Nadeau, Lise, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Nagel, Robert, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Nagy, Elmer, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Nickrenz, Scott, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Norville, Hubert, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Notley, Norman, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - O'Riley, Christopher, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Otis, Cynthia, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Owens, Dewey, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Palardy, Theresa Maria, 1956 Jun 19; Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Palmer, Charles, Undated (Box Photographs 2)
  - Parnas, Leslie, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Peck, Sally, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Pelletteri, Louis, 1962-1988 (Box Photographs 3)
  - Pertis, Peter, Circa 1989; Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Polanski, Louis, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Posztai, Tibor, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Poyana, Raphael Antonio, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Provost, Richard, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Putsch, Tom, Undated (Box Shared Small Oversized 2)
  - Rabine, Eugene, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Rewinsky, Leo, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Rizzi, Victoriana, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Robb, Madelyn, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Robinson, Leo, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Rose, Leonard, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Routch, Robert, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Rozie, Rick, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Sayao, Bidu, 1983 Mar 22 (Box Photographs 3)
  - Sayevich, Ben, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Scafarello, Margaret, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Scelba, Anthony, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Schaffer, Robert, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Schapiro, Maxim, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Scholes, Kim, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Schorr, Fridrich, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Schorr, Virginia, Circa 1944; 1957 Sep 18; Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Schuller, Gunther, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Seeber, Leonard, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Segal, Rubin, 1930-1955 (Box Photographs 3)
  - Shelton, Lucy, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Silva, Luigi, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Silverherz, Dorothy, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Simpson, Claire, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Singleton, Kenneth, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Sinta, Donald, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Small, Rosemary, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Smith, David, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Smith, Gordon, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Smith, Julia, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Snyder, Kerala, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Soulos, George, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Spekter, Edythe, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Steffan, Sophia, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Swallow, John, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Terry, Kenton, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Treger, Charles, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Treggor, Philip, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Trisler, Joyce, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Tolo, Leland, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Uppman, Theodor, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Urban, Virginia, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Veri, Frances, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Verrilli, Norma, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Walker, John, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Weiner, Mildred, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Wells, David, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Werner, Donald, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Westerman, Kenneth, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Willens, Joyce, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Willet, William, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
  - Willheim, Imanuel, Undated (Box Photographs 3)
- Compositions
  - Bauer, Harold (Box Compositions OV 1)
  - Bergner, Carl (Box Compositions OV 1)
  - Bloch, Ernest (Box Compositions OV 1)
  - Broadhead, Edward Hall (Box Compositions OV 1)
  - Del Paincyse ? (Box Compositions OV 1)
  - Dinerstein, Norman (Box Compositions OV 1)
  - Epstein, Alvin, 2 Folders (Box Compostions OV 2)
  - Freed, Isadore, 2 Folders (Box Compositions OV 3)
  - Hoffman, Allard (Box Compositions OV 3)
  - Jacobi, Frederick (Box Compositions OV 4)
  - Kopmar, Israel (Box Compositions OV 4)
  - Lischner, Rose (Box Compositions OV 4)
  - Mulready (Box Compositions OV 4)
  - Sellars, James (Box Compositions OV 5)
  - Sydeman, William (Box Compositions OV 5)
  - Weigal, Karl (Box Compositions OV 5)
  - Bloch, Ernest (Box Compositions 1)
  - Broadhead, Edward Hall (Box Compositions 1)
  - Epstein, Alvin (Box Compositions 1)
  - Finney, Ross Lee (Box Compositions 1)
  - Freed, Isadore (Box Compositions 1)
  - Giannini, Vittorio (Box Compositions 1)
  - Iadone, Joseph (Box Compositions 1)
  - Jacobi, Frederick (Box Compositions 1)
  - Katz, David (Box Compositions 1)
  - Kroll, William (Box Compositions 1)
  - Lepak, Alexander (Box Compositions 1)
  - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai (Box Compositions 1)
  - Macbride, David (Box Compositions 1)
  - Maxwell, Robert (Box Compositions 1)
  - McKown, Marguerite (Box Compositions 1)
  - Paranov, Moshe (Box Compositions 1)
  - Sellars, James (Box Compositions 1)
  - Sydeman, William (Box Compositions 1)
  - Weigel, Karl (Box Compositions 1)
- Duplicates, 2 Folders (Box Shared Small Oversized 3)